Guide to the Washington State Nurses Association Records
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- WASHINGTON STATE NURSES ASSOCIATION, 1908-1980; RECORD GROUP I
  - CORRESPONDENCE, SERIES IV
    - General Correspondence, 1912-1979; SUBSERIES I (Box-folder 1/4-1/13, 15/20-16/21, 29/1-29/42, 39/35-40/18, 49/15-51/14, 61/1-62/19, 71/1-71/2)
      - Washington State Board of Medical Examiners, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 50/23)
      - Washington State Board of Nursing, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 50/24)
      - Washington State Board of Nursing - job specs and salary ranges, 1973 (Box-folder 50/25)
      - Washington State Board of Nursing - legal action, 1970 (Box-folder 50/26)
      - Washington State Board of Nursing - recommendations for appointments, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 50/27)
      - Washington State Board of Nursing - recommendations for appointments, 1973 (Box-folder 50/28)
      - Washington State Board of Pharmacy, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 50/29)
      - Washington State Board of Practical Nurse Examiners, 1966-1972 (Box-folder 50/30)
      - Washington State Committee for Rural Development, 1973 (Box-folder 50/31)
      - Washington State Comprehensive Health Planning Advisory Council, 1973 (Box-folder 50/32)
      - Washington State Council on Aging, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 50/33)
      - Washington State Council on Higher Education, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 50/34)
      - Washington State. Department of Social and Health Services, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 50/35)
      - Washington State. Division of Vocational Education, 1965-1971 (Box-folder 50/36)
      - Washington State Governor -- appointments to agencies, boards and commissions, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 51/1)
      - Washington State Interagency Council on Smoking and Health, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 51/2)
      - Washington State Journal of Nursing, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 51/3)
      - Washington State Journal of Nursing, 1971 (Box-folder 51/4)
      - Washington State Journal of Nursing, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 51/5)
      - Washington State. Nursing Home Advisory Council, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 51/6)
      - Washington State. Superintendent of Public Instruction, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 51/7)
      - Washington State Health Facilities Association, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 51/8)
      - Washington State Heart Association, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 51/9)
      - Washington State Hospital Association, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 51/10)
      - Washington State League for Nursing, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 51/11)
      - Washington State Medical Association, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 51/12)
      - Washington State Operating Room Nurses Association, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 51/13)
      - Western Interstate Council for Higher Education, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 51/14)
      - General correspondence, 1974 (Box-folder 61/1)
      - General correspondence, 1975 (Box-folder 61/2)
      - Advisory group representation, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 61/3)
      - Board of Directors, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 61/4)
      - Executive Committee, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 61/5)
      - Executive Director, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 61/6)
      - Interoffice memos, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 61/7)
      - American Society of Association Executives, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 61/8)
      - Area Health Education Center for Southwest Washington, 1974 (Box-folder 61/9)
      - Group Health Cooperative Women's Caucus, 1974 (Box-folder 61/10)
      - International Council of Nurses, 1974 (Box-folder 61/11)
      - Forrest T. Jones & Company, 1974 (Box-folder 61/12)
      - King County Medical Blue Shield, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 61/13)
      - Federal legislation, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 61/14)
      - Washington State legislation, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 61/15)
      - Licensed Practical Nurses Association, 1974 (Box-folder 61/16)
      - Long-term Care Regional Education Center Advisory Board, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 61/17)
      - National Student Nurses' Association, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 61/18)
      - New York State Nurses Association, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 61/19)
      - Other state nursing associations, 1974 (Box-folder 61/20)
      - Other state nursing associations, 1975 (Box-folder 61/21)
      - Parliamentarian, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 61/22)
      - Phoenix Mutual Life Insurance Company, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 61/23)
      - President's correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 61/24)
      - Professional Services Department, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 61/25)
      - Professional Services Department, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 61/26)
      - Public relations, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 61/27)
      - Regional Education Center, 1975 (Box-folder 61/28)
      - State Federation of Specialty Nursing Organizations, 1974 (Box-folder 61/29)
      - State of Washington Associated Nursing Students (SWANS), 1974 (Box-folder 61/30)
      - U. S. Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1974 (Box-folder 61/31)
      - Washington Coalition for a National Health Program, 1974 (Box-folder 61/32)
      - Washington Society of Association Executives, 1974 (Box-folder 61/33)
      - Washington State Board for Community College Education, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 61/34)
      - Washington State Board of Examiners for Nursing Home Administrators, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 61/35)
      - Washington State Board of Health, 1974 (Box-folder 61/36)
      - Washington State Board of Health, 1975 (Box-folder 61/37)
      - Washington State Board of Medical Examiners, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 61/38)
      - Washington State Board of Nursing, 1973 (Box-folder 61/39)
      - Washington State Board of Nursing, 1974 (Box-folder 61/40)
      - Washington State Board of Nursing -- recommendations for appointment, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 61/41)
      - Washington State Board of Pharmacy, 1975 (Box-folder 61/42)
      - Washington State Board of Practical Nurse Examiners, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 61/43)
      - Washington State Comprehensive Health Planning Advisory Council, 1974 (Box-folder 61/44)
      - Washington State Council on Crime and Delinquency, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 62/1)
      - Washington State. Department of Social and Health Services, 1974 (Box-folder 62/2)
      - Washington State. Department of Social and Health Services, 1975 (Box-folder 62/3)
      - Washington State. Governor, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 62/4)
      - Washington State. Governor, 1975 (Box-folder 62/5)
      - Washington State. Governor -- recommendations for appointments, 1975 (Box-folder 62/6)
      - Washington State Health Facilities Association, 1974 (Box-folder 62/7)
      - Washington State Journal of Nursing, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 62/8)
      - Washington State Journal of Nursing, 1976 (Box-folder 62/9)
      - Washington State Journal of Nursing, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 62/10)
      - Washington State Journal of Nursing, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 62/11)
      - Washington State Medical Association, 1974 (Box-folder 62/12)
      - Washington State Medical Association, 1976 (Box-folder 62/13)
      - Washington State Medical Association, 1977 (Box-folder 62/14)
      - Washington State Pharmaceutical Association, 1974 (Box-folder 62/15)
      - Washington State Pharmacy Consortium, 1975 (Box-folder 62/16)
      - Washington State Special Education Advisory Council, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 62/17)
      - Washington State Women's Council, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 62/18)
      - Women's Auxiliary to the Washington State Medical Association, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 62/19)
    - Organizational Mailings, 1966-1978; SUBSERIES II (Box-folder 16/22-18/5, 29/43-29/44, 51/15, 62-20-62/11)
      - Board of Directors, 1966 (Box-folder 29/43)
      - Board of Directors mailings (part 1 of 2), 1967 (Box-folder 16/22)
      - Board of Directors mailings (part 2 of 2), 1967 (Box-folder 16/23)
      - Board of Directors mailings (part 1 of 6), 1968 (Box-folder 16/24)
      - Board of Directors mailings (part 2 of 6), 1968 (Box-folder 16/25)
      - Board of Directors mailings (part 3 of 6), 1968 (Box-folder 16/26)
      - Board of Directors mailings (part 4 of 6), 1968 (Box-folder 16/27)
      - Board of Directors mailings (part 5 of 6), 1968 (Box-folder 16/28)
      - Board of Directors mailings (part 6 of 6), 1968 (Box-folder 16/29)
      - Board of Directors mailings (part 1 of 5), 1969 (Box-folder 16/30)
      - Board of Directors mailings (part 2 of 5), 1969 (Box-folder 16/31)
      - Board of Directors mailings (part 3 of 5), 1969 (Box-folder 16/32)
      - Board of Directors mailings (part 4 of 5), 1969 (Box-folder 17/1)
      - Board of Directors mailings (part 5 of 5), 1969 (Box-folder 17/2)
      - Board of Directors mailings (part 1 of 5), 1970 (Box-folder 17/3)
      - Board of Directors mailings (part 2 of 5), 1970 (Box-folder 17/4)
      - Board of Directors mailings (part 3 of 5), 1970 (Box-folder 17/5)
      - Board of Directors mailings (part 4 of 5), 1970 (Box-folder 17/6)
      - Board of Directors mailings (part 5 of 5), 1970 (Box-folder 17/7)
      - Board of Directors mailings (part 1 of 7), 1971 (Box-folder 17/8)
      - Board of Directors mailings (part 2 of 7), 1971 (Box-folder 17/9)
      - Board of Directors mailings (part 3 of 7), 1971 (Box-folder 17/10)
      - Board of Directors mailings (part 4 of 7), 1971 (Box-folder 17/11)
      - Board of Directors mailings (part 5 of 7), 1971 (Box-folder 17/12)
      - Board of Directors mailings (part 6 of 7), 1971 (Box-folder 17/13)
      - Board of Directors mailings (part 7 of 7), 1971 (Box-folder 17/14)
      - District mailings, 1966 (Box-folder 29/44)
      - District mailings (part 1 of 2), 1967 (Box-folder 17/15)
      - District mailings (part 2 of 2), 1967 (Box-folder 17/16)
      - District mailings (part 1 of 2), 1968 (Box-folder 17/17)
      - District mailings (part 2 of 2), 1968 (Box-folder 17/18)
      - District mailings (part 1 of 2), 1969 (Box-folder 17/19)
      - District mailings (part 2 of 2), 1969 (Box-folder 17/20)
      - District mailings (part 1 of 3), 1970 (Box-folder 17/21)
      - District mailings (part 2 of 3), 1970 (Box-folder 17/22)
      - District mailings (part 3 of 3), 1970 (Box-folder 17/23)
      - District mailings (part 1 of 3), 1971 (Box-folder 17/24)
      - District mailings (part 2 of 3), 1971 (Box-folder 17/25)
      - District mailings (part 3 of 3), 1971 (Box-folder 18/1)
      - District mailings, 1972 (Box-folder 51/15)
      - District mailings (part 1 of 2), 1978 (Box-folder 62/20)
      - District mailings (part 2 of 2), 1978 (Box-folder 62/21)
      - Commission on Nursing Practice mailing (part 1 of 4), 1971 (Box-folder 18/2)
      - Commission on Nursing Practice mailing (part 2 of 4), 1971 (Box-folder 18/3)
      - Commission on Nursing Practice mailing (part 3 of 4), 1971 (Box-folder 18/4)
      - Commission on Nursing Practice mailing (part 4 of 4), 1971 (Box-folder 18/5)
    - American Nurses' Association Correspondence, 1958-1978; SUBSERIES III (Box-folder 18/6-19/13, 30/1-30/19, 40/19-41/13, 51/16-52/34, 62/22-63/11)
      - General correspondence (part 1 of 2), 1958-1965 (Box-folder 30/1)
      - General correspondence (part 2 of 2), 1958-1965 (Box-folder 30/2)
      - General correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 40/19)
      - General correspondence, 1963 (Box-folder 40/20)
      - General correspondence, 1964 (Box-folder 40/21)
      - General correspondence, 1965 (Box-folder 40/22)
      - General correspondence (part 1 of 2), 1963-1965 (Box-folder 30/3)
      - General correspondence (part 2 of 2), 1963-1965 (Box-folder 30/4)
      - General correspondence, 1966 (Box-folder 30/5)
      - General correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 30/6)
      - General correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 18/6)
      - General correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 18/7)
      - General correspondence, 1971 (Box-folder 51/16)
      - General correspondence, 1972 (Box-folder 51/17)
      - General correspondence, 1973 (Box-folder 51/18)
      - General correspondence, 1974 (Box-folder 62/22)
      - General correspondence, 1976 (Box-folder 62/23)
      - General correspondence, 1977 (Box-folder 62/24)
      - Advisory Council, 1970 (Box-folder 18/8)
      - American Journal of Nursing, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 18/9)
      - Annual report data, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 18/10)
      - Capital Commentary, 1967 (Box-folder 18/11)
      - Central billing (part 1 of 2), 1967-1970 (Box-folder 18/12)
      - Central billing (part 2 of 2), 1967-1970 (Box-folder 18/13)
      - Clinical conference, 1969 (Box-folder 18/14)
      - Community planning for nursing education, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 18/15)
      - Disaster nursing, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 18/16)
      - Exchange visitor program and immigrant nurses, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 18/17)
      - Friday mailings, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 18/18)
      - Friday mailings (part 1 of 3), 1968 (Box-folder 18/19)
      - Friday mailings (part 2 of 3), 1968 (Box-folder 18/20)
      - Friday mailings (part 3 of 3), 1968 (Box-folder 18/21)
      - Friday mailings (part 1 of 2), 1969 (Box-folder 18/22)
      - Friday mailings (part 2 of 2), 1969 (Box-folder 18/23)
      - Friday mailings (part 1 of 2), 1970 (Box-folder 18/24)
      - Friday mailings (part 2 of 2), 1970 (Box-folder 18/25)
      - Friday mailings (part 1 of 2), 1971 (Box-folder 18/26)
      - Friday mailings (part 2 of 2), 1971 (Box-folder 18/27)
      - Intergroup relations, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 18/28)
      - Job descriptions for association employees, 1958-1966 (Box-folder 18/29)
      - Medical Advisory Board on Educational Film Production (part 1 of 2), 1970 (Box-folder 18/30)
      - Medical Advisory Board on Educational Film Production (part 2 of 2), 1970 (Box-folder 18/31)
      - Membership correspondence, 1967 (Box-folder 19/1)
      - Membership correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 19/2)
      - Membership correspondence: various districts, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 19/3)
      - Membership correspondence: District #2, 1969 (Box-folder 19/4)
      - Membership correspondence (part 1 of 3), 1969-1970 (Box-folder 19/5)
      - Membership correspondence (part 2 of 3), 1969-1970 (Box-folder 19/6)
      - Membership correspondence (part 3 of 3), 1969-1970 (Box-folder 19/7)
      - Organizational Services Department, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 19/8)
      - Position paper: educational preparation for nurse practitioners and assistants to nurses, 1967 (Box-folder 19/9)
      - Public relations, 1967 (Box-folder 19/10)
      - Public relations, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 19/11)
      - Public relations and press releases, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 19/12)
      - Report schedule, 1967 (Box-folder 19/13)
      - American Journal of Nursing, 1966 (Box-folder 30/7)
      - American Nurses' Association Conference Group on Psychiatric Nursing, 1958-1966 (Box-folder 30/8)
      - Capitol Commentary, 1966 (Box-folder 30/9)
      - Committee on Historical Source Materials in Nursing, 1966 (Box-folder 30/10)
      - Economic Security Program, 1960-1969 (Box-folder 30/11)
      - Economic security report to American Nurses' Association, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 30/12)
      - Fair employment practice laws, 1964 (Box-folder 30/13)
      - Federal aid to nursing education, 1956-1963 (Box-folder 30/14)
      - Legislation, 1959-1964 (Box-folder 30/15)
      - Position papers, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 30/16)
      - Practical Nursing associations, 1964-1968 (Box-folder 30/17)
      - Surgeon General's speech, 1966 (Box-folder 30/18)
      - Visitors' Observer Program, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 30/19)
      - American Nurses' Association memos (part 1 of 4), 1964 (Box-folder 40/23)
      - American Nurses' Association memos (part 2 of 4), 1964 (Box-folder 40/24)
      - American Nurses' Association memos (part 3 of 4), 1964 (Box-folder 40/25)
      - American Nurses' Association memos (part 4 of 4), 1964 (Box-folder 40/26)
      - American Nurses' Association memos, 1965 (Box-folder 40/27)
      - Annual report of state nursing associations, 1957-1958 (Box-folder 40/28)
      - Annual report of state nursing associations, 1959-1961 (Box-folder 40/29)
      - Annual report of state nursing associations, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 40/30)
      - American Journal of Nursing, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 40/31)
      - American Nurses' Foundation (part 1 of 2), 1962-1965 (Box-folder 40/32)
      - American Nurses' Foundation (part 2 of 2), 1962-1965 (Box-folder 40/33)
      - American Nurses' Foundation fundraising campaign (part 1 of 2), 1958-1964 (Box-folder 40/34)
      - American Nurses' Foundation fundraising campaign (part 2 of 2), 1958-1964 (Box-folder 40/35)
      - Careers Committee memos, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 40/36)
      - Careers Committee reports, 1967 (Box-folder 40/37)
      - General Duty Nurses Section, 1962-1967 (Box-folder 40/38)
      - Head Nurse Section, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 41/1)
      - Legislation, 1959-1960 (Box-folder 41/2)
      - Legislation, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 41/3)
      - Legislation, 1963 (Box-folder 41/4)
      - Legislation, 1964 (Box-folder 41/5)
      - Legislation, 1965 (Box-folder 41/6)
      - Nursing Service Administrators Section, 1957-1967 (Box-folder 41/7)
      - Office Nurse Section, 1955-1966 (Box-folder 41/8)
      - Private Duty Nurses Section, 1960-1965 (Box-folder 41/9)
      - Public Health Nurses Section, 1953-1965 (Box-folder 41/10)
      - Recruitment report, 1968 (Box-folder 41/11)
      - Study Committee on Functions and Structure of the American Nurses' Association (part 1 of 2), 1961-1965 (Box-folder 41/12)
      - Study Committee on Functions and Structure of the American Nurses' Association (part 2 of 2), 1961-1965 (Box-folder 41/13)
      - Academy of Nursing, 1972 (Box-folder 51/19)
      - Advisory Council, 1971 (Box-folder 51/20)
      - Advisory Council, 1972 (Box-folder 51/21)
      - Advisory Council, 1973 (Box-folder 51/22)
      - American Journal of Nursing, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 51/23)
      - Annual report of state nursing associations, 1968 (Box-folder 51/24)
      - Annual report of state nursing associations, 1969 (Box-folder 51/25)
      - Annual report of state nursing associations, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 51/26)
      - Annual report of state nursing associations, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 51/27)
      - Bylaws, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 51/28)
      - Candidates for office, 1972 (Box-folder 51/29)
      - Capital Commentary, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 51/30)
      - Centralized billing, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 51/31)
      - Commission on Economic and General Welfare, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 51/32)
      - Commission on Nursing Research, 1973 (Box-folder 51/33)
      - Commission on Nursing Service, 1968-1970 (Box-folder 51/34)
      - Committee on Common Interests and Goals, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 51/35)
      - Congress for Nursing Practice, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 51/36)
      - Congress for Nursing Practice, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 51/37)
      - Continuing education, 1969-1973 (Box-folder 51/38)
      - Division on Practice -- community health nursing, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 51/39)
      - Division on Practice -- maternal and child health, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 51/40)
      - Division on Practice -- medical-surgical nursing, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 51/41)
      - Division on Practice -- psychiatric and mental health, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 51/42)
      - Economic Security Program, 1972 (Box-folder 52/1)
      - Executive Director, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 52/2)
      - Field Service, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 52/3)
      - Financial crisis, 1970 (Box-folder 52/4)
      - Financial systems study, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 52/5)
      - Friday mailings (part 1 of 3), 1972 (Box-folder 52/6)
      - Friday mailings (part 2 of 3), 1972 (Box-folder 52/7)
      - Friday mailings (part 3 of 3), 1972 (Box-folder 52/8)
      - Friday mailings, 1973 (Box-folder 52/9)
      - Geriatric nursing practice, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 52/10)
      - Government Relations Department, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 52/11)
      - Honorary membership pins, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 52/12)
      - Insurance program, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 52/13)
      - Mary M. Roberts awards, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 52/14)
      - Membership promotion, 1966-1971 (Box-folder 52/15)
      - Membership promotion, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 52/16)
      - Nominations for office, 1971 (Box-folder 52/17)
      - Nominations for office, 1973 (Box-folder 52/18)
      - Committee appointments, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 52/19)
      - News releases, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 52/20)
      - Organization, staff and orientation, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 52/21)
      - Pilot project for recruitment of new graduates, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 52/22)
      - Platform, 1967-1971 (Box-folder 52/23)
      - Public relations, 1967-1972 (Box-folder 52/24)
      - Publications, 1968-1973 (Box-folder 52/25)
      - Regional executives conference, 1969-1972 (Box-folder 52/26)
      - Regional executives conference, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 52/27)
      - Regional medical programs, 1968 (Box-folder 52/28)
      - Salary goals and economic security, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 52/29)
      - State conventions, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 52/30)
      - State nursing association legislative activities, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 52/31)
      - State officials report, 1967-1970 (Box-folder 52/32)
      - Study of characteristics of membership in six state nursing associations, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 52/33)
      - Task force on American Nurses' Association systems, 1971 (Box-folder 52/34)
      - American Journal of Nursing, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 62/25)
      - Annual report to American Nurses' Association, 1974 (Box-folder 62/26)
      - Honorary Nurse Practitioner Award, 1973 (Box-folder 62/27)
      - Mary Mahoney Award, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 62/28)
      - Pearl McIver Public Health Nurse Award, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 62/29)
      - Bylaws, 1974 (Box-folder 62/30)
      - Council on Continuing Education, 1974 (Box-folder 62/31)
      - Department of Government Relations (part 1 of 3), 1974 (Box-folder 62/32)
      - Department of Government Relations (part 2 of 3), 1974 (Box-folder 62/33)
      - Department of Government Relations (part 3 of 3), 1974 (Box-folder 62/34)
      - Department of Government Relations (part 1 of 2), 1976 (Box-folder 62/35)
      - Department of Government Relations (part 2 of 2), 1976 (Box-folder 62/36)
      - Department of Government Relations (part 1 of 3), 1977 (Box-folder 62/37)
      - Department of Government Relations (part 2 of 3), 1977 (Box-folder 62/38)
      - Department of Government Relations (part 3 of 3), 1977 (Box-folder 62/39)
      - Department of Government Relations (part 1 of 2), 1978 (Box-folder 63/1)
      - Department of Government Relations (part 2 of 2), 1978 (Box-folder 63/2)
      - Friday mailings, 1974 (Box-folder 63/3)
      - Department of Economics and General Welfare, 1974 (Box-folder 63/4)
      - Department of Economics and General Welfare, 1975 (Box-folder 63/5)
      - Department of Economics and General Welfare, 1976 (Box-folder 63/6)
      - Department of Economics and General Welfare, 1977 (Box-folder 63/7)
      - Department of Economics and General Welfare, 1978 (Box-folder 63/8)
      - International Women's Year, 1974 (Box-folder 63/9)
      - Year of the Nurse, 1977 (Box-folder 63/10)
      - Membership promotion, 1974 (Box-folder 63/11)
  - FINANCIAL RECORDS, 1918-1977; SERIES V (Box-folder 1/14-1/26, 30/20-30/21, 63/12-63/13, 71/4)
    - Treasurer's reports, 1918-1936 (Box-folder 30/20)
    - Financial statement, 1943 (Box-folder 30/21)
    - Financial statements, 1967 (Box-folder 71/3)
    - Budget and financial reports, 1974 (Box-folder 63/12)
    - Budget and financial reports, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 63/13)
    - American Nurses' Association dues receipts, 1953-1957 (Box-folder 1/14)
    - Internal Revenue Service form 990, 1948-1959 (Box-folder 1/15)
    - Personal property tax affidavit, 1957-1959 (Box-folder 1/16)
    - American Nurses' Association Relief Fund, 1923-1937 (Box-folder 1/17)
    - Payroll memos, 1949-1953 (Box-folder 1/18)
    - Medical Arts Building office, 1956 (Box-folder 1/19)